<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="error_log_collection_k">"CONSENT TO PROVIDE DIAGNOSTIC AND USAGE DATA

Samsung would like your help in improving the quality and performance of its products and services. Samsung and its affiliates may collect diagnostic and usage data from your device for service improvement and statistical purposes, and also to track and address diagnostic events such as unexpected shutdowns and system errors. Diagnostic and usage collection may include usage information on how you use applications, log information on errors, and details on your use of applications (its specific function, frequency of use, memory/battery usage). All diagnostic and usage data will be collected and used in an aggregate manner only in a form that does not personally identify you or your device, and stored for 7 months separately from any other data we may collect. The diagnostic and usage data may be used and disclosed to other parties in accordance with Samsung's privacy policy. Since Samsung servers are located all over the world, the data we collect may be stored at servers, and disclosed to recipients, located outside your country including in Singapore, South Korea and the United States. You may choose not to provide us with any diagnostic and usage data, and such decision will not impact the functionality or operation of your device in any way. You may also choose to disable the collection of your diagnostic and usage information at any time via Settings. The Samsung privacy policy contains information about how you can access and seek correction of your personal information and how you may make a complaint about Samsung's collection, use or disclosure of your personal information and how Samsung will deal with such a complaint. By clicking on the “Yes” button below, you hereby agree to the collection, use, storage, sharing and disclosure by Samsung and its affiliates of diagnostic and usage data from your device for the purposes set out above and in accordance with Samsung’s privacy policy."</string>
</resources>
