<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="guide_samsung_legal_for_na">"By tapping Next or otherwise using the phone, you agree to Samsung's terms and conditions."</string>
    <string name="error_log_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="error_log_no">No thanks</string>
    <string name="error_log_collection">"You agree to provide Samsung the error log data from any Software Update failure your device experiences. This will assist Samsung to improve and enhance Samsung's Software Update process and ultimately help you keep your device properly updated."</string>
    <string name="validation_email">Checking Samsung account…</string>
    <string name="continue_for_a11y">To enable Accessibility mode, continue holding the screen with two fingers until you hear a beep.</string>
    <string name="canceled_a11y">Accessibility mode not enabled.</string>
    <string name="enabled_a11y">Accessibility mode enabled.</string>
    <string name="terms_confirm">I understand and agree to the terms and conditions above.</string>
    <string name="terms_title">EULA &amp; Diagnostic Data</string>
    <string name="terms_title_upgrade">End User License Agreement</string>
    <string name="settings_license_activity_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="settings_license_activity_unavailable">Error occurred while loading.</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank you!</string>
    <string name="data_connect_title">Data network</string>
    <string name="data_connection_text">Many applications, widgets, and services on your device, or that you access through your device, require an Internet connection. If Wi-Fi is not turned on, the device will connect to your mobile network, which may result in additional charges depending on your payment plan.</string>
    <string name="reactivation_lock_title">Reactivation lock</string>
    <string name="reactivation_lock_desc">Protect your device in case it is lost or stolen by stopping other people from reactivating your device after it has been reset. You need a Samsung account to use this service.</string>
    <string name="reactivation_lock_desc2">Before you request a repair under the warranty, the reactivation lock must be disabled. Remember your Samsung account information so you can reactivate your device when it is locked. To disable the reactivation lock, go to Settings > Security.</string>
    <string name="reactivatio_check_text">Enable the reactivation lock</string>
    <string name="device_name_title">Device name</string>
    <string name="device_name_warning">Enter device name.</string>
    <string name="device_name_desc">Enter a device name to easily identify your device when using Bluetooth, Wi-Fi Direct or tethering.</string>
    <string name="device_name_desc_wifi_only">Enter a device name so you can easily identify your device when using Bluetooth and Wi-Fi Direct.</string>
    <string name="key_feature">Browse key features</string>
    <string name="app_name">Samsung setup wizard</string>
    <string name="welcome_start_msg">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="key_feature_button">Learn more</string>
    <string name="tap_to_learn_more">Tap to learn more.</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_message">Device is set up and ready to use.</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select language</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="sim_missing_title">Insert SIM card</string>
    <string name="sim_missing_text">"Power off your device and insert your SIM card into the SIM card slot. If you prefer to skip this step now, be sure to insert your SIM card later. Until you do, most of your device's features will not work."</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_title">Use Google location</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_message">Google location service uses data from sources such as Wi-Fi and mobile networks to help apps to determine your approximate location, even when GPS is not available.</string>
    <string name="yes_agree">Allow Google location services to collect anonymous location data. This will occur even when no applications are running</string>
    <string name="yes_agree_use_location">Use My Location for Google search results and other Google services.</string>
    <string name="opt_set_title">Optional setting</string>
    <string name="opt_set_msg">"Easy mode helps you to use your device more easily with the easy widgets feature and the ability to customize the font size
Tap the easy mode tickbox to enable."</string>
    <string name="easy_btn_text">Enable easy mode set up?</string>
    <string name="try_again_button_label">Try again</string>
    <string name="skip_button_label">Skip</string>
    <string name="next_button_label">Next</string>
    <string name="next_button_disable">Disabled</string>
    <string name="button_tts">Button</string>
    <string name="previous_button_label">Previous</string>
    <string name="restart_button_label">Restart</string>
    <string name="finish_button_label">Finish</string>
    <string name="uim_missing_text">"Turn off your device, remove the battery, and carefully insert your UIM card with the gold contact side down. The cut-off corner should end up farthest away from the battery.
If you prefer to skip now, be sure to insert your UIM card later. Until you do, most of your device’s features will not work."</string>
    <string name="sim_uim_missing_title">No UIM/SIM card inserted.</string>
    <string name="sim_uim_missing_text">"Turn off your device and carefully insert your UIM/SIM card into the UIM/SIM card slot. If you prefer to skip this step now, make sure you insert your UIM/SIM card later. Until you insert it, most of your device's features will not work"</string>
    <string name="activation_progress_text">Activating your device. This can take a few minutes. Please wait…</string>
    <string name="activation_succ_title">Device activated</string>
    <string name="activation_succ_text">Your device needs to restart to be fully activated.</string>
    <string name="activation_fail_text">Your device couldn’t be activated. This may occur some temporary problem. Restart your device to activate again.</string>
    <string name="network_charges_title">Network charges</string>
    <string name="network_charges_text">Using some applications, such as Internet, Email, etc., and performing some actions using mobile networks, may incur additional charges. For example, mobile networks are required to register a Samsung account, and use widgets, live wallpapers, and information tickers. More information about network charges will be provided in other circumstance</string>
    <string name="network_charges_mobile_warning">Connecting via packet data may incur additional charges. Continue?</string>
    <string name="opt_dual_sim_msg">Enabling dual SIM always on lets you receive calls from both SIM cards even during calls.</string>
    <string name="dual_simi_btn_text">Enable dual SIM always on?</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_favorite_message1">Favorite Apps</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_favorite_message2">Favorite Contacts</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_favorite_message3">Favorite settings</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_favorite_message4">Simple alarm clock</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_favorite_message5">Picture frame</string>
    <string name="easy_step_widgets_skip_message">Tap Next to enable easy mode.</string>
    <string name="easy_step_font_message">Customize font size for Messaging, Email, Contacts etc.</string>
    <string name="tiny">Tiny</string>
    <string name="small">Small</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="large">Large</string>
    <string name="huge">Huge</string>
    <string name="easymode_label">Easy mode</string>
    <string name="easy_mode_summary">Use a simpler home screen layout, and larger text and icons.</string>
    <string name="easy_mode_help">Use your device more easily with a simpler home screen layout and application interactions. Larger text and icons will also be applied to your home screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_easy_mode">Enable easy mode</string>
    <string name="more_information">More information</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="talkback_description">You can enable Talkback by drawing a rectangle anywhere on the screen without releasing.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_description">Tap Accessibility below to change the accessibility settings.</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_title_baidu">Baidu location service</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_message_baidu1">Baidu location service uses data from sources such as WLAN and mobile networks to help apps determine your approximate location, even when GPS is not available. You can change this option any time under Settings.</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_message_baidu2">When the NLP function is installed and opened, Baidu location services will collect anonymous location data. This will occur even when no apps are running. Some data may be stored on your device.</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_message_baidu3">This may incur additional charges. The data collected will be used to find your location and improve accuracy. We ensure that your data will not be shared with other parties or be used for purposes other than providing services. The following data will be collected.</string>
    <string name="location_sharing_message_baidu4">"- ID, signal strength of WLAN AP to be surveyed from the periphery
- ID, signal strength to be surveyed from the peripheral base station (for GSM and CDMA)"</string>
    <string name="yes_agree_baidu">Allow Baidu location services to collect anonymous location data. This will occur even when no applications are running.</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_always_available_summary">Allow network location services and applications to scan for WLANs, even when WLAN is turned off.</string>
    <string name="date_time_auto">Automatic date and time</string>
    <string name="date_picker_title">Date</string>
    <string name="time_picker_title">Time</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_msg">Enable data access over mobile network.</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_title">Mobile data</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_connected">Device connected to mobile network.</string>
    <string name="stms_version">SM-G900F_EUR_20141215_0200</string>
    <string name="welcome_start_msg_att">Welcome to AT&amp;T Ready2Go!</string>
    <string name="email_account_r2g">Email accounts</string>
    <string name="att_terms_conditions">AT&amp;T Ready2Go Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="label_AcctYahoo">Yahoo</string>
    <string name="label_AcctHotmail">Hotmail</string>
    <string name="label_AcctAOL">AOL</string>
    <string name="label_Setup_Othermail">Other accounts</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_r2g">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_done">Done</string>
    <string name="home_sync_thankyou">Thank you!</string>
    <string name="home_sync_easy_setup">Easy setup</string>
    <string name="home_sync_easy_setup_msg1">"1. Turn on NFC on your mobile device. Then place your mobile device on top of the HomeSync device to install the HomeSync application.
2. Use the HomeSync app on your mobile device to control the HomeSync device. (Alternatively, you can control the HomeSync device using a mouse.)"</string>
    <string name="home_sync_easy_setup_msg2">You can connect an Ethernet cable instead of connecting to a Wi-Fi network.</string>
    <string name="home_sync_wifi_msg">To access the Internet, connect to a Wi-Fi network or connect an Ethernet cable.</string>
    <string name="home_sync_display_aspect_ratio">Aspect ratio</string>
    <string name="home_sync_display_aspect_ratio_msg">For a better picture display, manually set the aspect ratio of your TV using your TV remote control.</string>
    <string name="home_sync_nfc_tag">You can connect an Ethernet cable instead of connecting to a Wi-Fi network.</string>
    <string name="welcome_desc_for_mum">"Your user area has been added to this tablet.
After you have finished setting up, you can use the current applications and install new ones.

Important:

- The tablet's owner can uninstall the apps you have installed and delete your user area.
- Other users can allow changes to application permissions on your behalf.
- As with any computer, you should only share this tablet with people you trust."</string>
    <string name="background_traffic_text">Background data optimization will be enabled. This function automatically controls the amount of background data being received via mobile networks. This will save battery power and reduce data consumption. This function will not affect your normal use of the device.</string>
    <string name="data_usage">Data usage</string>
    <string name="location_activity_title">Google and your location</string>
    <string name="location_agree_sharing_content">"Allow apps to estimate your location with Google's location service. Anonymous location data will be collected and sent to Google, and may be stored on your device. Collection may occur even when no apps are running."</string>
    <string name="location_agree_use_search_content">"Get more relevant information when using Google apps. GPS and Google's location service may be accessed, even when you're not using Google apps."</string>
    <string name="location_agree_use_wifi_scan_content">"To improve location accuracy and for other purposes, Google's location service and other apps can scan for nearby Wi-Fi networks, even when Wi-Fi is off."</string>
    <string name="cu_registration_title">Register with China Unicom</string>
    <string name="cu_registration_message_1">Your device information will be sent to the China Unicom server to register your device during the first boot-up. It uses data from sources such as WLAN and the mobile network. This may result in additional charges.</string>
    <string name="cu_registration_yes_agree">I understand and agree to the terms and conditions above.</string>
    <string name="ctc_registration_title">Register device with China Telecom</string>
    <string name="ctc_registration_message_1">Your device information will be registered with the China Telecom server. The registration will use WLAN or Mobile data. Connecting to a mobile network may result in additional charges depending on your payment plan.</string>
    <string name="ctc_registration_yes_agree">I agree to this.</string>
    <string name="v3_title">Vaccine-driven information</string>
    <string name="v3_info">"For consumer protection in accordance with government policy, the antivirus program is installed and running.

The antivirus program V3 was installed with real-time monitoring and periodic updates.

Connecting to mobile networks may incur extra charges depending on your plan.

Real-time monitoring and automatic updates can be changed in the antivirus program settings."</string>
    <string name="dsa_dual_sim_always_on">Dual SIM always on</string>
    <string name="label_SamsungAccount">Samsung account</string>
    <string name="label_SamsungAccountDesc">Sign in or create a Samsung account to get the most out of your device.</string>
    <string name="msg_sec_acct_modify_disabled">To edit account, complete setup wizard and go to Settings > Accounts.</string>
    <string name="insert_sim_card">Insert SIM card</string>
    <string name="insert_sim_card_message">Insert SIM card to access network services.</string>
    <string name="insert_uim_card">Insert UIM card</string>
    <string name="insert_uim_card_message">Insert a UIM card to access your mobile network.</string>
    <string name="insert_simuim_card_message">Insert a UIM/SIM card to access network services.</string>
    <string name="data_usage_enable_mobile">Mobile data</string>
    <string name="ctc_data_warning_in_roaming">"You're now in the international roaming state, the mobile data is on, please pay attention to the local charge rates."</string>
    <string name="dlg_know">I know it</string>
</resources>
